<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on READ MY STUFF</title>
    <link>https://jysandy.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on READ MY STUFF</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 11:43:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jysandy.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beating a dead horse</title>
      <link>https://jysandy.github.io/posts/falling-to-your-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 11:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jysandy.github.io/posts/falling-to-your-death/</guid>
      <description>A clip from a certain popular influencer was doing the rounds on social media recently.
https://twitter.com/MintBlitz/status/1452794539668693000
I think I missed the bus when BRs became the be all, end all game mode of FPS. I could probably write an entire article on the flaws and failings of the genre, so for now, I&amp;rsquo;ll just say that not every FPS release needs to have a battle royale gamemode.
This doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be a zero-sum game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MMOs in 2021?</title>
      <link>https://jysandy.github.io/posts/new-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 11:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jysandy.github.io/posts/new-world/</guid>
      <description>I think the last time I&amp;rsquo;d played an MMO was somewhere around 2008. Before that, however, MMOs were a huge part of my gaming life growing up. Runescape (or what is known today as &amp;ldquo;Old School Runescape&amp;rdquo;) was my first MMO and also the first online game I ever played, and it was so long ago that it ran as a Java applet (remember those?) in your web browser. It was technically simple enough that it ran on the hand-me-down IBM Thinkpad I was using at the time, and it was full of features that were completely new to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initial Post</title>
      <link>https://jysandy.github.io/posts/initial-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jysandy.github.io/posts/initial-post/</guid>
      <description>For a long time, I never felt like I had anything to blog about. I never thought I had anything interesting or useful to put out there. I work as a programmer, but I&amp;rsquo;ve never really been interested in writing that type of content. I think I don&amp;rsquo;t want to produce tutorials or help articles because I don&amp;rsquo;t really consume that kind of content myself. They go out of date, are sometimes poorly written or even factually inaccurate, and I just don&amp;rsquo;t find them worth the hassle when I could read official documentation or a well-edited book instead.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
